# SHEME HAMITAJ



### Contact

#### Address:

Tirana, Albania

#### Phone:

+355 68 46 833 47

#### **Email:**

shen.i@live.com

#### Website:

https://shemehamitaj.com

### Languages

Albanian – Native
English – Excellent
Turkish – Excellent
Italian – Good

# Skill Highlights

- Strategic planning
- Problem solving
- Quick learning
- Communication

# Play Store Apps

 https://play.google.com/sto re/apps/dev?id=908394600 6672030470

### Summary

Computer Engineer experienced in Robotics(ROS), Computer Vision, Embedded Systems, Desktop, Mobile & Web Apps. Programming languages include C, C++, Java, Javascript, Typescript, Python, C# etc. Currently working with Vue & NuxtJS and PHP & Laravel.

# Experience

### circuly GmbH (Bielefeld, Germany)

Backend Lead Developer: 12/2022 - Present

- Organizing work, prioritizing features and creating tasks.
- Reviewing pull requests and making sure of code quality.
- Planning and executing deployments to production
- Gradual feature release via Unleash feature flags.

**Full Stack Developer:** 10/2021 – 12/2022

- Responsible for detailed feature planning and implementation on frontend and backend simultaneously.
- Payment processing via Adyen, Stripe, Braintree and Mollie.
- Dynamic email generation via html templates and simple self-created template engine.

Front End Developer: 01/2021 - 10/2021

- Developing new features and functionality for the web application based on user requirements and feedback.
- Writing clean, maintainable, and reusable code using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript frameworks such as Vue.js and NuxtJS.
- Implementing responsive web design techniques to ensure that the web application was optimized for all screen sizes.
- Writing automated tests using Jest and Cypress to ensure that the web application was functional and error-free.

Kocaeli University (Kocaeli, Turkey) AMR Developer: 08/2019 – 08/2020

> Work with a diverse team of electric and electronic engineers to create and develop AMR with SLAM & natural navigation.

### Education

Bachelor of Science: **Computer Engineering** – Completed, 2020 **Kocaeli University**, Turkey

# Scientific Papers

### A Survey of ROS Security -10/07/2019

**IWW2019**(10th International Conference on Image Processing, Wavelet and Applications)

# Certificates & Awards

### OBSS Code Master 2019 (hackathon) -19/12/2019

3rd Place at Kocaeli University

**IELTS Academic** – 14/07/2020 C1 Level : Score 7.5 out of 9.0